The upstarts of the great
pirate era have gained a
momentum that not even the world
government is prepared for.
During this exciting age,
there's one man standing at the
epicenter of everyone's attention.
Monkey D.
Luffy and his crew, the Straw Hats.
In order to stay ahead
of these turbulent times.
Every four years, 50 global leaders hold a
world summit in the holy land of Marijua.
This event, known as the
reverie, is about to begin.
The fate of the world is about
to take a dramatic new turn.
I'm drinking.
You know I don't like to be
interrupted when I'm drinking.
Yes, of course, sir.
We all know.
But, uh...
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
What do you want?
I wanted to give you a warning.
Straw Hat is on his way to you right now.
Is that supposed to scare me?
It shouldn't, if you
keep your hands off him.
Just sit tight, I'll head to the land of
Wano and take care of that rat myself.
You gotta be screwing with me, hell no!
Don't be so sensitive, it's not about you.
I have a personal matter
to settle with him.
And if I don't take his head
myself, then I'll lose face.
Beyond that, his crew took something
of mine and I want it back.
I don't care!
If I recall, you owe me a bit of a favor?
Do I now?
goodness don't tell me you
forgot that was a long time ago
maybe so but it's a lifelong debt
whatever
grudge you have
against this Straw Hat kid I
promise you mine is greater
I'll be the one who kills that
punk if you test me Lin Lin
I'll kill you too try it then.
This is a warning.
I didn't call to ask for your opinion
It's fine.
I'll lop his head off and be done.
We should be friends just
like old times, right?
Big mom is on the move seems
like she's going to meet up
with Kaido I can't believe they're
using an unsecured channel.
Surely they'd know we'd wiretapped
Them, what's their angle?
Are they trying to provoke us?
We should be friends just
like old times, right?
One emperor is enough trouble, but
two is just plain unmanageable.
We would need an admiral or
a couple warlords at least,
so you want me to go
check it out, Sakazuki?
I think that would be a Mistake.
This isn't one who they've got
highly skilled warriors there.
The samurai.
Caribou are you listening?
Kaido and big mom are
meeting up and they're
going after Straw Hat in
other words your grandson.
That's funny!
I'm afraid I don't see
the humor in this at all.
Your grandson aside, we can't allow
two of the four emperors to team up.
What do you expect us to do?
Like it or not, the
reverie's going on right now.
All our marines are busy
taking care of royalty.
So we just sit here?
Ain't no coincidence, ma 'am.
We're talking about Big Mom.
She knew Tang well we'd be
short on soldiers, Otherwise,
I reckon she wouldn't have been
so bold about this whole business.
Yes, I'm sure you're right, but still.
Well, what did the boss man have to say?
He said that the land of Wano
is a non-affiliated country,
so it's outside our jurisdiction.
I thought so.
Better to mind her own business, then.
I don't know, Garp.
If Big Mom and Kaido team up,
the Navy will have some major
consequences to deal with.
And you should know.
They're the reason you were
considered a Navy hero.
You mean the Rocks, huh?
Funny.
I figured you'd be too young
to know about them, Hina.
Before Roger showed up,
it was their era for sure.
But that was 40 years ago.
The past is the past.
They may have lost their captain,
but they're not any weaker for it.
It worries me a bit.
Eh, it's fine.
Maybe they'll come back.
But the world's full of maybes.
That's what makes it so fun.
Grinning again, are you?
I don't get it Enter King
Stella of Goa Kingdom
this is it the center of the world
now make your pledge huh
can i sit on the throne
first i don't think it's
appropriate to joke about
such a thing no man king
or otherwise may rest
upon that seat huh it's
called the empty throne,
for all nations of the
world are on equal standing,
and all rulers must pledge to
respect each other's sovereignty.
The weapons that you see here laid
before the throne were placed there 800
years ago to represent an oath made by
the first 20 who formed the modern world.
This spot lies at the
very center of the world,
and the fact that none sit upon
the throne is a symbol of peace.
The greatest authority in the
government is held by the five elders,
who are the highest ranking
among the Celestial Dragons.
However, even amongst them,
that power is divided.
There is none who would be
called King of the World.
Now, King Stella, it's
time to make your pledge.
If I sit on that chair, I'll
be the boss of everyone.
Are you feeling ill?
Let me sit there!
Come on, let's go!
Get away!
I got one, I got one!
A big, big mermaid, and she's
all mine now! Shirahoshi!
We're not stopping him?
I cannot abide by this no
matter the circumstances.
We must save her!
That's enough wiggling, Miss Fishy!
Get those chains off! Hurry it up!
Let her go! Careful! Stay back, princess!
You'll get yourself killed that way!
No, he's a celestial dragon! You can't!
Why should I care about that? Let me go!
Common sense doesn't apply to them!
They'll burn down every last inch
of Dressrosa if you make them mad!
Hey, that big jerk!
Don't do it, Leo! Shirahoshi.
Stop making this hard on me!
Lay it cool, everybody!
How'd you win?
Nice work, Slave Three.
Everyone will be so jealous
when they see my cute new pet.
I can't stand by and watch this.
How dare you do this
to Luffy Land's friend?
Liam, no!
Dammit, I guess this is it.
Hold on, I'm coming for
you, Mermaid Princess!
Someone stop that guy from Candy!
It's not worth it!
Let me go!
Leo!
Who the hell are you, creeps?
I think some gratitude
is in order first. Kaku!
Sorry for both zero.
If we hadn't stopped your little outburst,
several countries might
have met their end.
Don't stand against the Celestial
Dragons, even a kid knows that much.
Cypherpole is a secret
organization under the world
government specializing in
intelligence and assassination.
Aegis Zero is its most powerful
unit under the Celestial Dragons.
Cy! I am!
The celestial dragons descended from
the gods who created this world.
Royalty or not, you exist
in a realm beneath them.
If a god desires something of
yours, it must be granted to them.
Finally, one of you morons gets it!
You call this justice?
It doesn't make any sense!
A god is not required to make sense.
Otohime, this can't be the
world you've dreamed of.
Where we would live under
the same sun as humans.
You know this isn't
right, make him stop it.
Wait, princess of Alabasta.
King Neptune.
Thank you.
I won't forget your kindness,
brief as our friendship was.
And I'm sorry that you
have to witness this.
I'll split their skulls and return
to the bottom of the sea for good.
Stop it!
I know how you feel, but you can't!
If this is what life is like on the
surface, the dream was dead from the start!
Loki, Neptune! You can't give up!
Don't let the worst examples
of mankind speak for all of us!
Forgive me, my love!
No!
We'll face the humans together!
And maybe then, we can finally
make a difference for the future!
For our children!
For the island!
Even if it's just a small one!
Even if we bare our hearts
to them, humans won't change!
I must save Shilohoshi!
This is the only way!
You defy me!
Cypherpawn, kill him now! Good! Yes, sir.
Step aside!
Please, King Neptune, listen to reason!
No, Father, please don't do it!
Please don't give it to hatred!
Someone hit a celestial
dragon! Who was that?
I have nothing to do with this!
Nobody look at me!
None of you!
As a fellow celestial dragon,
I'm ashamed to see such behavior.
Please forgive us!
He's a world noble, too?
Let go of the princess, you dolt!
My apologies to everyone.
This fool brought savagery
to your peaceful event.
Since you look surprised, I assume
you don't remember me, Neptune.
But I owe the Ryugu kingdom a great debt.
And I have been awaiting
this day for many years.
The day that you would come here.
Oh, no.
It can't be.
I'm a foolish celestial dragon who drifted
down to the Ryugu kingdom a decade ago,
lost and injured.
I need you to save my life, filthy fools!
It was the eloquent words of the
late queen that gave me my humanity.
So now I will do anything
in my power to aid you.
King Neptune, it is my honor
to welcome you to Mariejoie.
Go, Cypherpole!
Retreat from here!
You've traveled quite a long way.
This must be important; it's the
reverie now, considering your status.
I should think you'd have the
sense to stay out of politics,
but we're willing to honor
your request this time.
Thank you.
That's very kind.
Now then, would you
excuse us for a moment?
Yes, sir!
I need to speak to you
about a certain pirate.
I'm surprised at how few people are left.
It's hardly a surprise
after something like that.
I doubt anyone wants to get tangled
up in unwanted trouble, you know.
Wow!
There, all better.
How do you feel?
All of the bruises have
completely disappeared.
Thanks a lot, Manchili.
That was just like magic.
What a wonderful power.
How cute.
The biggest and the smallest princesses.
It's quite a spectacle
to see you two together.
I'm sorry I was afraid of you.
That was awfully rude of me.
It's all right, Mom Cherie.
There's no need to beat yourself up.
Realistically speaking, all countries
have both good and bad people.
We fishmen are no exception
to that rule either.
You have my gratitude, Myoscar.
Thanks to you, I could
keep my promise to Otohime.
There's no need to thank me.
In fact, Neptune, consider this
payment for saving me long ago.
During the seven-day conference, I
promised to look after Princess Shirahoshi.
Honestly, I'm thankful my status is
finally helping someone for once.
So then I can kick the Celestial Dragon's
butts and say that it was in order?
I was told I was supposed to
keep my hands off of them,
but if you give me permission...
Oh, sure.
I will gladly take
responsibility for that.
Please, do what you must
to protect the princess.
Now ain't that something.
It's hard to believe one
of them's got a heart.
Princess Phoebe!
My most sincere apologies.
Are you all right?
I heard that there was some trouble.
Sorry, I should have never left your side.
Don't worry, pal.
I'm doing fine.
Anyway, how's my father?
King Cobra's occupied at the moment.
He's with Fujitora, that one
admiral who sent the letter.
He wants to speak to King Rick.
Let's give them time.
Pangaea Castle.
It has three entryways outside of its main
gate, all of which are heavily guarded.
One of those gates belongs
to the Celestial Dragons.
It leads to the Land of the Gods,
This is where these nobles reside.
Stop! State your name!
Wyatt's Queen Dowager Connie
of the Sorbet Kingdom.
Hello, ma 'am.
The land of the gods
lies beyond this point.
I'm afraid that it's far too
dangerous for you to proceed.
Please, return to the castle.
The pain!
This is unforgivable!
Damn that, dear Scott!
St.
Charles, please calm down!
You'll open your wounds!
That man will pay.
Oh, my word!
Hey, open the gate! Huh?
What's going on here?
St.
Charles is injured!
He needs medical assistance
immediately! Right away!
Move it! To the doctor!
My goodness, Jarnos!
How are you faring after
your recent incident?
Oh, my poor boy.
After I heard the news,
I rushed over to get you.
Say, Roswell, sir!
Huh?
Father, is that you?
Tell me, how did this happen?
Oh, my beloved son.
Huh?
Where's the Queen Dowager?
That blasted don't kill
them, yes God must pay!
Unreal!
What kind of celestial dragon
refuses to keep even a single slave?
He's just like that kook homing who
descended to the lower world 30 years ago.
The Don Quixote family has some nerve.
That big bunch of lunatics.
Oh, I didn't realize,
Father, you brought him?
The Invincible Slave, Kuma.
Well, of course I did.
It was finally my long-awaited turn to
take him for a spin on the rental list.
Oh, wow, that's great.
The invincible slave makes
a fine steed, Father.
The wait was surely worth it.
Who knew a warlord would make such
a fine mode of transportation?
And it's so much fun to hit him.
You can stab him, too.
He doesn't scream, either.
He's truly the finest slave of them all.
He's glorious, Father.
I want one, too.
Oh, oh, oh.
If I don't die first.
Are you okay, sir?
Let's keep it down.
Ow, ow, ow.
I've really had a rotten
time since everyone got here.
Oh, my poor Chalus.
Let's summon the world's greatest
position to fix you up, shall we?
I didn't expect to run into
him out in the open like that.
At least I made it inside.
I'll make sure they all pay.
I swear it!
Damn it!
Cool your jets, Sabo.
Golly, you boys can be so scary.
scary you're telling
me you're not angry you
saw what those monsters
are doing to our comrade
they're torturing that
poor kind-hearted man
they'll pay for this
calm down we feel you it really is
terrible i promise that we won't
leave kuma in that state after
all that's the reason we're here
The problem is, even if we free him, I'm
afraid he won't return to his former self
All his life,
Kuma was a victim of the world
government's oppression in one
way or another They made an example
out of him It was a warning, right?
No one's safe from us, even
kings of allied nations.
Those who defy the gods will all be
brought to their knees without question?
They have the whole Navy and CP0 on
their side, more than anyone can handle.
We can't screw up and get caught.
I know.
We won't.
Either we succeed, or die.
The much-anticipated event,
The Reverie, commences.
The seas of the world are divided
into four bodies of water.
They're split one way by a massive
continental wall known as the Red Line.
And split the other way by a dangerous
stretch of sea known as the Grand Line.
Within these waters lies the New
World where Luffy is traveling.
The World Government is
a massive organization
encompassing most of the world's nations.
170 in total.
Every four years,
50 Chosen Rulers are
sent to this Holy Land to
represent their nations
in important negotiations.
Which one is my seat?
At long last. Indeed.
Tell me, how's your country been?
You said pirates left it
in ruin four years ago.
They're locked up and in Pell-Daho,
courtesy of Fleet Admiral Sakazuki.
Which reminds me, who is this boy I keep
hearing about in the news? You know.
You mean Straw Hat Luffy?
He made an attempt on Big Mom's life,
and it's rumored that he has
his sights set on Kaido next.
Fancy that.
The Emperor?
Then I wonder what's going to
happen in the land of Wano.
They don't participate in the world
government, so needless to say,
it's practically a lawless land.
If that's the case, I must raise the
question, can we even consider them a nation?
Perhaps we should make
that our business, then?
It's hardly that simple.
The navy costs money.
Trouble seems to follow that Strawhead
Luffy wherever he goes, doesn't it?
He sounds like a bear.
Tell me about it!
What's so funny, Prudence?
Hmm, Luffy.
As always, we have a new chairman.
Who's up now?
It's me!
Hello there, everyone.
It's Bollywood, huh?
Greetings.
Excellent.
He'll run this efficiently.
Let's get started.
We have quite a lot to address.
The most influential rulers in all
four seas begin their discussions.
Together, they will reshape the world.
Now, without further ado,
let's commence the debate.
For seven days, my fellow noblemen, we
shall speak of this beautiful world of ours.
This is the Reverie.
It seems like the conference has begun.
While on that subject,
Cobra, the King of Alabasta, is
requesting a special meeting with us.
The Nefertari family, huh?
How interesting!
They were the only family
of the first twenty who
stayed in the Lower World
eight hundred years ago.
So then, in a sense, they're traitors.
Has he noticed something out of sorts?
Let's hope he doesn't
overcomplicate things for us.
Worrisome times, Big Mom
and Kaido are trouble.
This started with the war of the best,
and now I fear it can't be stopped.
The balance of the world
can't be maintained forever.
This we all know.
With that in mind, I believe the time has
come for a great cleansing, gentlemen.
Great emu, they have arrived.
Thank you.
Have you decided upon which light
is to be extinguished, great lord?
Who will be cleansed from history?
Speak, lord, and share their name.